Well, why don't you show me
this so-called proposal?
Okay, I'll show you my proposal!
Here it is! This is the completed
version of my proposal!
How do you like it?
What is that?
It's...
You jerk!
Momma, it's weird! It's strange!
Don't point!
But that weird thing is really weird.
But it's really, really strange!
You can't say so just because
it's the truth!
She's right, kid.
If you pay attention to something like
that, the weirdness will rub off on you.
That's right!
But it's strange!
Everybody knows it's strange.
Yes, he's right!
But you can't say it out loud because
she might hear you.
Dragon Slave!
Mistress Lina?
Mistress Lina!
What do you think of it?
How do you...
*Your offer is*
*absolutely rejected and denied*
*from the beginning!*
Why? Didn't you say you would
cooperate with my proposal?
This proposal is a completely
different story!
The wings of a dragon,
the neck of a sea serpent,
a blast demon's body and your head:
the Super Chimera!
I'm sure you'll have more fun this way!
Even if you use a copy of me,
it would really bother me to see a
Chimera walking around with my face!
Don't worry.
I'm going to use you, not a copy.
Is that so? Well, in that case...
That's even worse!
You snuck out by yourself while
I was taking my beauty rest.
I guess you are plotting to steal
someone's treasure,
but I won't let you do so, Lina lnverse!
So, you finally woke up,
you perverted magic user.
Who are you calling a perverted
magic user?
What's that?
Oh, well, I was asking her to cooperate
with me to create a creature like this.
It's so cool!
I like your idea and I'm
going to help you.
Wait! What are you thinking, Naga?!
You're still a little kid,
aren't you, Lina?
You don't understand this design
which is full of functional beauty.
Exactly!
Mono Bolt!
Followed by Black Occult Blast!
Explosion Array!
Hey, Lina.
We wasted it, didn't we?
Wasted what?
The plan to make you into a Chimera.
Excuse me Naga, but it
was a month ago.
I'd finally started to forget
that incident.
I won't let you forget it.
Listen, who was it that blasted
me along with that old man?
It was an accident.
Are you Lina lnverse?
That's me all right.
I want you to come with us without
asking any questions.
What are you going to do if I say no?
Do you mean to take me
with you by force?
I guess that's what we'll do.
You're very brave to ignore me.
Who the hell are you?
Now!
Explosion Array!
Now, you're the only one left,
aren't you?
Impossible!
I can't believe you'd involve your
companion in the blast!
Naga will be fine, really.
Really, you say?
I hope you don't think you'll make it
home unharmed after crossing me.
I guess I escaped from her somehow.
*Hello?*
Hi!
You're a ghost!
That's not a very polite thing to say.
I've just been following you from
the air while you were running.
Well, let's see now.
Oh, no! That voice is...
They were pretty good, but they
couldn't handle you, could they?
It's okay. Get out of here now!
Thank you very much!
Long time no see, Lina lnverse.
Just as I thought, you're that Chimera
manic, old man Diol.
That's correct.
Haven't you learned your lesson yet?
Your strength is certainly
what caught my eye.
However, with these guys it
will be a different story!
You've raised some interesting
points, haven't you?
What kind of technique did you use?
Are you familiar with
"Copy Homonuclus"?
The making of a golem by
mixing animal bones,
magical herbs and human
blood, isn't it?
Exactly.
I've taken those methods
one step further.
With Copy Homunculus for example,
I made it easier.
I can create a golem using just a
strand of hair or a finger nail.
Add to this the fact that you've
been to my lab before.
It was not so difficult for me to find
one of your hairs on the floor.
I see, I see.
Wait a second!
I guess he made ten copies of me.
However, even though he can make
a copy with my abilities,
I don't think he can copy my memories,
experiences or techniques.
That means they can't use my magic.
If you think using them will help
you win, bring them on!
Well, I guess I will. Everybody!
What are these?!
Lina...
There's one missing.
I guess she caught him and forced
him to buy her a meal.
Lina's so spoiled!
It's that laughing sound again.
Mom, I'm scared.
Scary, so scary!
Please, please, please, please...
Looking good, Lina lnverse.
She looks just like a little girl when
she's sleeping like this.
Your band of thieves was ruined
by that little girl, wasn't it?
Are you trying to be sarcastic?
Ah, no. What I meant was
I don't want you to be violent with her
even though you harbor a grudge.
This girl, Lina lnverse, is necessary
material for my project.
I know that. You've told me
so again and again.
That's why I'm here.
And why you became my
sponsor, right?
You've said that again and
again, Lord Vista.
Anyway, Master Diol, let's move
her to our base quickly,
so we can create the Chimera.
Well, why don't you slow
down a little bit?
There are still a few other
things I need to collect.
I see. I don't care what they are,
just tell me what you need.
Okay, then I need you to get me
a brass demon, a red dragon,
and a Serpent of the Deep.
One of each, please.
I wonder if you have any of the
necessary materials at all?
Let me ask you something,
young man.
Which is more difficult: capturing a
dragon, a demon or Lina lnverse?
By the way, old man, what are you
going to do with those others?
The only thing they can do is laugh
loudly and give people headaches.
They eat and drink like horses. I can't
say my meal tickets have been light.
That's all very well, but...
It was most embarrassing for me to
order their outfits from the shop.
Have you seen this girl?
No, I haven't.
You've become even trickier and
more elaborate, Lina lnverse.
However!
You're kidding yourself if you
think this will confuse me!
She's started again!
Help me!
Please, please, please...
You where the one I heard laughing
like a horse this evening.
Please leave now. You don't
need to pay for anything.
A genius is always unappreciated
in her own day.
Hey, Master Diol!
Why are you being so noisy?
Word just arrived that the woman
called Naga has arrived in Midas,
and has been making inquiries.
I see.
I'll take care of it.
Long time no see, but I don't
remember your name.
I'm Diol.
I'm sorry to call you out like this, but
I can't return Lina lnverse to you.
You're wasting time if you think
talking that way
will keep me away from
your sweet deal!
I wonder if you're right or not?
All the materials for my Chimera
will be ready shortly.
Then, the strongest Super Chimera
ever will be born!
Don't make me laugh.
No matter what happens, I won't let
Lina cut me out of a free meal.
I don't think they understand
what they're talking about.
Neither of them seem to
care though, do they?
I see. If you really want Lina
lnverse back that badly,
you'll have to kill me first.
But you have to know it won't be easy!
Everybody!
How's that?
You're kidding yourself.
You ten copies over there!
Your laughing voices only copy
the surface of my laugh.
Do you really think you can take
over the world that way?
A supreme sense of superiority
and extreme self-confidence!
My laugh can't be copied
without these.
Since you don't have those qualities,
it will be over ten years before
you can laugh like me.
I can't take it any longer!
Oh, my God!
What's the matter with you?
That woman, Naga,
she might be even more fearful
than Lina lnverse!
What do you mean?
The copies I created, the copies
of her, MY copies...
They lost against the real one?
No, no, no! No!
They became attached to her.
They became attached to her?
It's the whole group!
Demonic Crystal!
Finally, I have found you, Lina lnverse!
I can't believe you hired strange guys
and tried to stop me
in order to keep the sweet
deal to yourself!
However, if you think you can get rid
of me that way, you're still a child.
Hey, you, you don't listen
to me at all, do you?
You didn't think taking sleeping pills
would make me give up, did you?
De-toxify!
Are you awake now, Lina?
Hey, Lina?
She's gone again. I guess she's
not mentally strong enough.
I have no choice now.
Hey, you girls, why don't you hide your
faces with your cloaks or something?
Lina! Hey, Lina!
Naga?
*What do you mean, "Naga"? You're*
*not totally awake yet, are you?*
Naga?
*What do you mean, "Naga"? You're*
*not totally awake yet, are you?*
Yeah, I had a strange dream
or something.
It wasn't a dream.
I guess you're fully awake now.
I already know that you hired
someone to stop me
in order to keep a sweet
deal all to yourself.
Admit your guilt and let
me share in the deal!
Excuse me, but what kind of
nonsense are you spouting?
I was captured by a magic user
and held here.
You know, old man Diol,
the Chimera maniac?
Do you really think I'll believe
such a stupid excuse?
It's not an excuse, it's true!
I fainted after seeing ten of
you lined up together.
It's really nothing but an excuse.
There isn't a human alive who would
faint because of something like that.
Damn, in this case...
Naga, that old man, Diol, tricked
us and he's going to
eat delicious things while we fight.
I thought so.
Listen, Lina and I are going
to chase the two of them.
Wait for us in Midas. Okay?
Say, won't the town be in a panic?
Don't worry. I'm sure they've
been immunized by now.
We swam so far I guess we'll be okay.
Right, Master Diol?
Damn.
What's the matter?
Lina, I left Lina lnverse back there.
We didn't have time to bring
her with us, did we?
You're right.
However, even though she'll sleep
for another half a day,
if they get together with Lina
after she recovers,
it could cause serious trouble.
You're already in serious trouble.
Good morning, Master Diol.
By the way, who are you?
I have no other choice now!
I'm Lord Vista, sponsor of this
old man's Chimera Plan.
I was the leader of the brigand gang
Boizun, which you ruined.
I had a beard at that time, so you
might not recognize me.
That's why you tried to
take revenge on me.
Isn't it?
Exactly.
Listen, don't even think that
you can defeat me now.
Now that I'm serious, I will...
Explosion Array!
Damn, I can't believe there are young
girls like her in this day and time.
She attacked us in the
middle of your line!
What kind of girl doesn't have
any morals or loveliness?!
Mega Brand!
Sorry!
I'm sorry. It's all our fault!
Well, let's take these two to the
federal office and get the reward.
We can't leave such a crazy old
man running around free.
I'll finally be able to eat
delicious food, right?
By the way, Naga, why are
those ten still with you?
It's obvious. It's my natural virtue.
I see, whatever you say.
Well, what are you going
to do about them?
Just pay them no mind.
Excuse me, but...
Are you worrying about how
much they'll cost us?
You're so narrow minded, Lina lnverse!
Somebody, please stop them.
I don't know what to decide to do,
I picture empty skies in my dreams
Why do we fight?
Why do we get hurt?
The dream that I hold in my arms
Sometimes becomes heavy
Happiness is the ecstasy
that everyone wants
They covet it and get it,
but still want more
If you have a limitless desire
you can regain your footing
If you want happiness is
The only thing you can
do is to keep walking
Some sacrifices are
impossible to discuss
Within a limitless desire
If you have passion and bravery
The only thing you can do
is keep walking
You said you want us to
make Jeffrey a man,
but even though Naga dresses this
way, our business isn't like that.
Oh, my God, what are
you talking about?
Who would ask to do such a thing
to my lovely Jeffrey?!
Well, first of all, my son Jeffrey is,
this might sound like I'm boasting
since I'm his mother,
but he listens to me all the time,
and is a very good boy.
He's grown up very upright, and
I'm extremely proud of him.
As the heir of the noble
Mailstar family,
how should I say this, he is a man
descended from noble blood,
he is overflowing with natural
talents that can't be hidden
no matter what one does.
Anyway, as his mother, it's natural
for me to think about him
and, considering my lovely
Jeffery's talents
and being true to the name
of the Mailstars,
want to find him a suitable job.
So I used my special channels
to gather information
and considered the question
thoroughly.
Since my family comes from a
long lineage of great knights,
I decided it would be natural for
him to join the Royal Guard.
Well, some other ladies may
feel that it's too natural,
but no matter what other ladies say,
I believe that becoming a knight is the
most suitable course for my Jeffery.
This isn't a bad job.
Excuse me...
Hello, I'm Jeffery Mailstar.
Well, our business is to help you
become a member of the Royal Guard.
Yes, my mama told me to help
you subjugate bad people.
Mama...
Your mama said?!
I know that the "bad people"
we're going to subjugate
are actors hired by that woman, but...
It's too late, Lina. We accepted
the payment in advance.
Well, we need to discuss how to go
about that. How is your skill at...
Oops, I wonder if she might
have seen me?
Is there anything wrong, Ms. Lina?
No, no, nothing, nothing.
Don't worry about me.
Anyway, we would like to know what
practical skills you have
before we do anything.
Please let yourself be relieved.
No matter what kind of enemies
appear in front of us,
I will kill them all just as
fast as they appear!
I understand that you've never
fought in any real battles.
So, where does your confidence
come from?
It's obvious!
Mama guaranteed my success
by saying, "You'll be fine!"
You're kidding yourself, boy.
No matter what your mother
told you, clumsy is clum...
I won't let anybody say bad things
about my lovely Jeffery!
My Jeffery's skill with a
sword is outstanding!
Excuse me, but are you...
Oh, my! Don't pay any attention to me!
I'm just a stranger walking by.
I guess she was just walking by.
Are you serious?
It's always been a very common
incident, happens all the time.
A masked pedestrian appears and
beats the hell out of someone.
It doesn't normally happen that way.
Really? Perhaps it's a local custom.
No way...
We're close to the thieves' hide-out.
Jeffery, what plan of attack
would you use?
Well, if it was my plan...
First, I'd introduce myself, and
begin a frontal assault.
I'd kill small fry one after another, and
march onward like a great angry wave.
I'd use my quick wits to rescue
the hostage, you Ms. Lina.
Finally, I would kill their leader,
and become a celebrity!
How was that?
You're asking me if it was a good plan?
It wasn't even a plan! It sounded
like a third-class minstrel's...
What do you mean "third-class"?!
My lovely Jeffery's plans
are never wrong!
They can't be! Right?
Excuse me...
Don't worry about me. I'm just
a pedestrian walking by.
I didn't realize there were tourists
in places like this.
Are you really serious?
Is there anything wrong with that?
No...
Hey, where are you going?
Are these the guys
Ms. Josephine hired?
It's a nice casting job.
There you are, you brigands!
Prepare yourselves!
Damn...
You jerks! You've caused
me such a struggle.
I'm sure you must be famous warriors!
What a stupid joke!
You clumsy fool!
Man, that's the wrong thing to say!
What did you say to my lovely Jeffery?!
You should let yourself be hit by my
Jeffrey's sword, just to be nice to him!
I thought so.
For your information,
I'm just a pedestrian.
Well, when I become serious,
this is the result.
Really?
Well, let's go! The enemy's
hide-out is very close.
Since you made it this far, I guess
the guards are finished, right?
Just in case though, did you
come to rescue them?
Them?
Yes.
When I finally returned to this place
after an extended absence,
these small fry were pushing
everyone around.
I wonder if they're also actors
hired by Josephine?
You do know them, don't you?
First, let me ask you something.
Are you a real band of thieves?
Is there such thing as a
fake band of thieves?
Anyway, I don't think we can
let you go unharmed
since you beat the hell out of
two of my followers.
Don't make me laugh!
I don't understand the detailed
background,
but my trusty rapier will be more than
enough to deal with a wimp like you.
Prepare yourself!
Take this!
Hey!
What's the matter? For such a
big mouth, you really stink!
Those words!
You shouldn't say things like that!
What?
You said my Jeffery stunk,
and I won't forgive you!
She's dead, isn't she?
What do you think you were doing,
using a chain to catch me?!
That was very dangerous!
It's you, the pedestrian just walking!
What is this monster?!
Oh, no! He drew blood!
I'm going to faint because I saw blood!
I'm so sensitive.
Me too.
Hey, what are you doing?
I don't really understand you,
but now you're the only one left.
Well, what are you going to do?
Explosion Array!
What was that?
What wimps!
You didn't do anything!
I'm going to do it right now!
Freeze Arrow!
I won't lose so easily!
Oh, damn!
Listen, little girls!
If you don't want to lose this kid,
cease your stupid struggling.
Naga, flank him.
Okay.
I said don't move! Don't move!
Do you want to know what
we're going to do now?
I said if you do something strange,
I'm going to kill him!
I'm going to show you now.
She's going to take off
her clothes now!
What?!
Come on...
Inverse Screw Crash!
Man, it's a sad living, isn't it?
Now you know, Jeffery.
Lina is exactly right. You're not cut
out for this kind of business at all.
Certainly, I'm just a beginner compared
to Ms. Lina and Ms. Naga.
But!
Even so, I understand that...
I understand that both of you say such
things because you envy my talent!
However, however, l...
Because of this incident...
I have absolute confidence
in myself now!
By using my incredible talent,
which frightens even me,
I will someday claim the title
of Knight of Knights!
Are you listening to me?
Hey, Ms. Lina! Ms. Naga!
Ms. Lina, Ms Naga!
Actually, a man called the
Dark Knight sometimes appears,
and his is followed by uncountable
number of Orcs.
They have robbed villages
and towns in this area.
Therefore, my mama told me,
if I defeat this Dark Knight with my
overflowing talents and your support,
she's sure that I would become
so popular that
the Royal Guard would
want me to join them.
With our...
Support?
You will accept our offer, won't you?
Is she a ghost or what?
How about the idea?
Of course we'll accept it.
It's too scary to refuse your offer.
Oh, I should have said we couldn't
be so unkind as to refuse.
Lord Jeffery!
The Dark Knight has appeared.
Roger! Prepare to take
the field right now!
Yes, Sir.
What was that?
My mama hired a private
royal guard for me.
Private?
Royal guard?
Who are you?
It's obvious!
We are the Golden Flame Knights,
gathered under the name of justice!
Hey, a name like that is
so embarrassing.
You jerk, our king's land should
be holy and inviolable,
but you've raped it with your dirty
feet and dastardly deeds!
Now, justice will...
Don't choke at a time like this.
Anyway, I'm going to kill
you so be prepared!
Are you ready! Charge!
How stupid!
You'll see whether they're stupid or not
after you actually fight against them.
Sounds interesting.
The first victims are the orcs!
Got it!
Fire Ball!
Wind Bomb!
You're magic users, aren't you?
Great job! I shouldn't underestimate
you even if you are women.
Bomb Split!
This is it! This is the battle!
The real battle!
Freeze Crystal!
That's because you talk too much!
What?
I see. I understand.
What do you understand?
Your armor is enchanted, isn't it?
Good guess.
I figure it's probably it's the
Enchantment of Valmashied.
It's very expensive to use that curse,
therefore, I'm sure you have some
kind of big sponsor behind you.
You're pretty clever, aren't you?
Tell me who your sponsor is,
and what you're plotting.
I have no idea what my
sponsor is thinking.
The only thing I'm interested
in is strength in battle.
If you want to me to answer
your question,
you have to win the battle against me.
All right then.
Chance!
Who is this idiot?
Did you just say "idiot"?!
Ms. Josephine, where did
you come from?
I didn't feel any trace of her presence.
That woman is very high level.
Anyway, you are extremely rude!
How can you call my
Jeffery an "idiot"?!
Shut up!
What's wrong with calling
an idiot an idiot?!
You still want to talk like that?
This mouth says...
Ms. Josephine?
She went back to where she was.
I couldn't even see her movement.
My name is Galda. Please let me
become your pupil, Ma'am.
Pupil?!
In that case, you have to work
under my Jeffery.
Under this kid?
Under this what?
I'm so sorry, Teacher!
Now listen to me.
You are going to work under
my Jeffery. Am I clear?
Yes, Ma'am!
See you later.
Lord Goldias will probably
be over there.
The sponsor you were talking about
before, right?
We've finally got our fight.
I don't mind fighting, but what are
we going to do with Jeffery?
I know he'll only be trouble
if we bring him with us,
but if I say something bad about
him, Ms. Josephine
will come out and beat
the hell out of us.
I have an idea!
The main character usually
appears last, doesn't he?
I'm sure it will be tough
for us without Jeffrey,
but if we do our best, he will revive
like a phoenix and fly to our aid!
Good job, Lina. Your way of saying
that won't cause a problem.
Good!
Now, believing in Jeffrey's revival,
we'll leave him behind this pillar.
Now, let's go!
I'm disappointed in you, Galda.
However, your betrayal means that
someone defeated you in battle.
There are some scary people
left in the world, aren't there?
Well, it's not a big deal.
Shall we start now?
Living Mail?
Exactly! Are you ready, Galda?
I have you, Galda!
Flare Arrow!
So!
This guy is really strong.
I'm going to help Galda by drawing
the Living Mail's attention.
Naga!
What?
I won't forget you!
Go and die!
Now, everything will be
all right except Naga.
Flow Break!
What?
If you think you can kill
me using Living Mail,
you're making a very bad mistake.
I didn't realize she knew Flow Break.
If I'm lucky,
the Enchanment of Valmasheed on
your armor has been dispelled.
You don't have any chance of
winning so be prepared.
I wonder if you're right or not?
That's it! Goldias, I'm going
to be your doom.
You...
You're finished.
Jeffrey, what are you doing here?
That voice! It's Papa!
Papa?
He's here, which means Josephine
must be here too!
Honey, can you explain
what's going on here?
Ah, well, that is, there's a long,
long story behind this, and...
Shut up! You wimp of a husband!
Mama!
Sometimes in this world,
mysterious things happen.
The wife looks like she's
not even a human,
and their son is lower than
a human being.
I can almost understand why
that man has been
committing crimes to
overcome his stress.
However...
Stop it!
*What?*
Please cut it out.
*Honey, what do you want to say?*
*Honey!*
Please cut it out.
*Honey, what do you want to say?*
*Honey!*
Somebody, help me!
I don't know what to decide to do,
I picture empty skies in my dreams
Naze arasou no?
Naze kizu tsuku no?
Kono ude ni takusarete
iru yume ga toki ni
Omoku naru no yo
Shiawase-tte, daremo ga
hoshigaru Ecstasy
Musabo-tte te ni shite,
soredemo motomeru
Kagiri nai yokubou ga areba
Tachi naoru koto mo dekiru
Shiawase o shiritai no nara
Aruki tsuzukeru shika nai
Kagiri nai yokubou no naka ni
Ie nu gisei mo aru kedo
Jo-netsu to yuuki aru nara
Aruki tsuzukeru shika nai
In the history of magic users,
there was one,
Shazal Rugandy, who was called great.
He lived around four hundred
years ago,
and had a strong talent for the
development of magical items.
Among his many inventions,
there was one called the Shadow
Reflector, a shadowy mirror.
It was originally invented as a
weapon to combat evil.
By reflecting a person in the mirror,
the mirror created
a shadow with the same skills as
the one who was reflected.
On top of that, the shadow
had a character
completely opposite to that
of the reflected person.
But people said that Shazard
sealed the mirror away
without introducing it to the world.
That's why it's existence was
treated as a rumor.
That is, until recently, when a magic
user uncovered an old record.
He reported the incident to the
Magic Users' Association
but as the Association was
organizing the investigation,
the related document was stolen
by an unidentified person.
The name of the thief was
discovered soon afterwards.
He's a magic user and Vice President
of the Association.
His name is Lagan.
His goal is obvious: to gain the
ultimate power before anybody else.
Think about it a second.
As long as his enemy exists, by
reflecting the enemy in the mirror,
he will be able to create a shadow on
his side with the same abilities as
his enemy, and it will be limitless.
Yes, even if he had only this mirror,
it would be easy to conquer the world.
In order to stop his designs, the
Magic Users' Association
has launched a counter plan.
They've requested the cooperation
of me, Naga,
as well as that of this other
one who was near me.
Who do you mean when you say
"this other one"?
It sounds like a cover story.
Yes, it does.
But it doesn't matter to us whether
there's a Shadow Reflector or not.
Why not?
Think about it.
They've requested that we play our
part separated from the Association.
We can take the mirror away from him,
or destroy it,
or capture Lagan, or kill him.
That means...
If we defeat Lagan before
the other groups,
including the Association's
main group...
The reward, two hundred
gold coins will be...
Yes, it will be ours.
I see.
Then, we're going to run straight there,
kill that magic user and get the reward!
I thought I heard women
laughing in here.
There are only two girls
without any weapons.
Are you one of Lagan's followers?
Lagan, Lakugan, stop
talking nonsense.
Well, hurry-up and give me
all your valuables!
Explosion Array!
Well now...
This should cover meal expenses.
Why don't we go now, Naga?
You did it again, Lina.
Well, it's routine, I have to do it.
Now, let's go and get those
two hundred gold coins!
I had a dream that I was falling,
stung by disappointing news
_Shitsubou no kakera ni sasare,_
_taorete yukujibun no yume mita_
I was shaking so hard I woke up
_Hidoku furue me ga samete_
In the middle of the night,
I felt I was left alone
_Yoru no naka de tori noko_
_sareta ki ga shita_
I'm lonely, I feel emptiness
_Samishii yo, munashii yo_
But I believe that the dream in
the real world won't die
_Keredo genjitsu no yume wa shindari_
_shinai to shinji teru yo_
I'm not alone if I have a friend
_Hitorija nai, nakama sae ireba_
I have strength to share with them
_Wakachi aeru tsuyosa ga aru kara_
To share even the mistakes
or happiness
_Ayamachi mo, yorokobi mo_
The mind is easily hurt
_Kokoro nan te sugu ni kizu tsuku shi_
But we can start over tomorrow
_Asu ni nare ba mata de naoseru shi_
I won't give up my dream,
and I won't lose today
_Yume o akirame nai, kyou ni makenai_
If I believe in my soul,
if I aim at the target
_lf I believe in my soul,_
_Hyouteki o mezase ba_
My soul, my heartbeat becomes faster
_My soul, kodou ga hayaku naru_
Hot, painful, heart-rending,
my way continues
_Atsuku, itaku, setsunaku,_
_michi wa tsuzuku_
Everybody up down, climbing
up and falling down
_Everybody up down, nobottari ochitari_
Up down, but don't give up
_Up down, dakedo kujike nai de_
Let's change everything in our power,
run all the way
_Subete chikara ni kae yoo,_
_run all the way_
The mind is easily hurt
_Kokoro nan te sugu ni kizu tsuku shi_
But we can start over tomorrow
_Asu ni nare ba mata de naoseru shi_
I won't give up my dream,
and I won't lose today
_Yume o akirame nai, kyou ni makenai_
If I believe in my soul,
if I aim at the target
_lf I believe in my soul,_
_Hyouteki o mezase ba_
My soul, my heartbeat becomes faster
_My soul, kodou ga hayaku naru_
Hot, painful, heart-rending,
my way continues
_Atsuku, itaku, setsunaku,_
_michi wa tsuzuku_
Everybody up down, climbing
up and falling down
_Everybody up down, nobottari ochitari_
Up down, but don't give up
_Up down, dakedo kujike nai de_
Let's change everything in our power,
run all the way
_Subete chikara ni kae yoo,_
_run all the way_
Oh, pretty!
Good, good. Hot, hot. I'm so happy!
Hey?
Good and hot! This is the way sweet
potatoes should be eaten.
Delicious! So delicious!
*Hey!*
Hot, hot!
Hey?!
So good. You can't have it!
HEY!
Shut up! I'm busy eating
baked sweet potato!
You're also chasing Lagan, aren't you?
Then you ought to go back.
He is protected by lycanthropes,
shape-shifters.
I see.
There are lots of them.
There were five in my group but now
they're all dead except me.
Oh, good, I'm done.
Well, see you later.
Hey, hey!
Wait, wait, wait!
What now?
What do you mean "what now"?
I'm telling you that two females
can't handle it!
Especially since one of
you is still sleeping.
She'll be all right. After a while, she'll
come along laughing loudly.
Also, and actually I'm boasting,
even if dozens of lycanthropes attack,
they won't be a match for us.
I see. Then, can you take me to the
village at the foot of this mountain?
No.
No?
You don't have any money, do you?
No, but I want you to...
Shut up. If you want us to help you,
you need to give us
something to make it worth our time.
I would expect you to understand
that since you're an adult.
I pretended to be injured and
was going to kill you
when you let your guard down.
Good job! You've already discovered
that I'm a follower of Lord Lagan.
Really? I didn't know that.
I thought you were trying to
trick us so you could
win the two hundred gold coins.
You didn't recognize me?
No.
Ah hem...
In this situation, the only thing
I can do is to kill you myself.
You make me laugh so hard.
Do you really think you can kill
me and this other one?
Excuse me, but who do you
mean by "this other one"?
That I am injured is a lie,
but the story about Lord Lagan being
protected by lycanthropes is true!
No way, are you one of them?
Exactly!
Look! This is my real shape!
I don't want to see anything like that!
I guess our enemies have
prepared for us.
They sure have. However, this guy
came to us, which means...
Perhaps...
Yes, it means we're the top team!
That means...
If we keep going at the same pace...
If we keep going...
All right!
The two hundred gold coins
will be ours!
In the eddying darkness, toward
the shining tomorrow
_Uzumaku yami no naka,_
_hikaru ashita ni mukai_
*Fire Ball!*
ln the eddying darkness, toward
the shining tomorrow
_Uzumaku yami no naka,_
_hikaru ashita ni mukai_
In the eddying darkness, toward
the shining tomorrow
_Uzumaku yami no naka,_
_hikaru ashita ni mukai_
With hope of freedom but
seeking restrictions
_Jiyuu o nozomi Nahgara_
_Sokubaku o motome teru_
*Freeze Arrow!*
With hope of freedom but
seeking restrictions
_Jiyuu o nozomi Nahgara_
_Sokubaku o motome teru_
With hope of freedom but
seeking restrictions
_Jiyuu o nozomi Nahgara_
_Sokubaku o motome teru_
To love someone, to be
loved by someone
_Hito o aisuru koto,_
_hito ni ai sareru koto_
Getting used to wanting something,
and getting lost in loneliness
_Motomeru koto ni nare te,_
_sabishisa ni mayotte iru_
*Garb Flair!*
Getting used to wanting something,
and getting lost in loneliness
_Motomeru koto ni nare te,_
_sabishisa ni mayotte iru_
Getting used to wanting something,
and getting lost in loneliness
_Motomeru koto ni nare te,_
_sabishisa ni mayotte iru_
Human meets human, and
becomes human
_Hito wa hito ni deai,_
_hajimete hito ni naru_
Meeting at this moment is
not a coincidence
_lma aeta koto wa, guuzenja nai kara_
If you want to become strong,
if you want to become kind
_Tsuyoku naritai nara,_
_yasashiku naritai nara_
Take good care of yourself,
more and more
_Motto, Motto, jibun o taisetsu ni shite_
If you want to know why you were
born, if you want kindness
_Umareta wake o shiritai nara,_
_yasashiku shite hoshii nara_
You can love someone on your
own, more and more
_Motto, motto, jubun kara aiseba ii_
When you get hurt, when
you hate yourself
_Kizu tsuita toki koso,_
_jibun ga iya na toki koso_
I'm sure you'll be able
to find tomorrow
_Kitto, kitto, hito wa asu o mitsukeru_
It's okay to stop and have a rest
_Tach-domatte yasumu no mo ii_
Until the day when you can
start to walk again
_Mata aruki daseru hi made_
I'm sure that the time
will come soon
_Kitto, kitto, sono toki wa_
_mou sugu soko_
Fire Ball!
You started a fire.
Please, please, please, please...
We've finally reached their hide-out!
Two hundred gold coins!
The dogs from the Association have
finally arrived, have they?
However, it's already too late!
Look at this!
This is the legendary mirror,
Shadow Reflector!
Shadow Reflector?
The Mirror of the Shadows...
I can't believe it really exists.
But there is no guarantee that the one
you have in your hands isn't a fake.
Exactly. That's why I've
been waiting for you.
Waiting for you to come here.
Now, I can determine if this mirror
is genuine or a fake.
Let's find out!
I did it! I did it!
Look! I finally have the ultimate power!
The legendary mirror really exists.
If the rest of legend is right,
the shadows have the same
knowledge and experience,
they are the same level as we are.
The definite difference is, as long
as we are Lagan's enemies,
the shadows will be Lagan's allies,
which means they are our enemies.
I was careless, but...
You're impressed, aren't you?
Well, here are the shadows!
Kill your enemy in front of you.
Fight! Fight against yourselves!
Are they really attacking us?
What the hell do they want to do?
Please, let's talk to each other.
What? What?
Boo hoo, boo hoo...
Hey, I said "fight"!
Fight? How barbarous!
Even if we call each other "enemy",
we're all human beings.
There are no really bad
people in the world.
If we talk, I'm sure you'll understand.
Right? You will understand me,
won't you?
Goose pimples, goose pimples!
I never imagined how scary I'd be if
I were feminine and a humanitarian.
Then what's happening to Naga?
I cant' wear an outfit like this!
Here!
Let go! No...
How scary the Shadow Reflector is!
It is truly worthy of being called
the ultimate weapon.
Well, how can I put this...
This isn't quite what I expected.
What shall we do, Lord Lagan?
You ask what we should do,
but in this situation...
What can I say?
Now I know why Shazal Rugandy
sealed that mirror away.
Even if this mirror creates peaceful
shadows of a hostile enemy,
nothing would be changed.
It will be a waste to break it,
but more importantly,
it's just to embarrassing
to leave it loose!
Embarrassing to leave it loose...
*Embarrassing to leave it loose...*
For the time being,
I'm going to run away!
Excuse me, but what about these?
Leave them!
Hey, I won't let you escape!
Please wait. What are you going
to do to Lord Lagan?
Are you asking me?
It's obvious! I going to beat him up
and take him to the Association!
Even if I tell her that, she'll
just keep hold of me,
and I'm sure she'll continue to
talk about human rights
or the need to talk or something
like that forever.
Ms. Lina!
I understand. Let's talk.
Really?
Boo hoo...
It's working! I'm pretending
I'm an easy going person
but actually I'm combating
her just by talking.
Listen carefully.
Lagan stole a document which
belongs to the Association,
and he plotted to keep the
Shadow Reflector to himself.
Oh, no...
It's true.
People from the Association will arrive
soon, and show you the evidence.
You'll understand the situation by
hearing the story from them.
Anyway, he has to expiate his guilt.
But...
I know you're on Lagan's side,
but, yes, that's why you have
a responsibility to make him
understand he has to pay!
I understand it will be hard for you,
but this is for him.
You're right!
Now that you've decided to do so,
let's hurry up and chase him!
Hey, Naga, stop passing out again
and again and come with us!
Hey, hurry up!
All right.
Excuse me, but shall I go with you?
I'm embarrassed to stay
here by myself.
I wonder which way he went?
They ran pretty fast, didn't they?
I guess Lagan and the others
came across
the other group from the
Association somewhere.
I'd guess so.
Damn! The Association shouldn't
waste my time!
The mirror is okay though.
Lord Lagan!
No way! Why is the shadow
helping you?!
Please!
Lord Lagan, stop doing scary
things like this, I beg you.
Surely, I respect you and love you,
but guilt is guilt.
Please, please throw your
weapon away!
If the shadow, which has an opposite
character is like this...
You, what kind of character
do you have then?!
None of your business!
That's okay. However, no matter
who's trying to catch me,
I'm going to run away and
never be caught.
That's why I brought this
mirror with me.
If I create the enemy's shadow,
even if the shadow doesn't
have the will to fight, it can be
used as a speed bump.
Lycanthropes, attack them!
Attack them and kill them!
I'm there!
I'm going to be with him until the end.
No! Don't!
How shameful...
What are you going to do
about those two?
I think the shadows will disappear
once the mirror is broken.
Let's break the mirror
during the battle!
I guess that's the only choice for us.
Well, let's go!
Freeze Arrow!
Bram Braizer!
It's over.
Everything's over, finally.
Excuse me...
Well, you had no choice, but...
I don't want to accept...
I don't like you using violence.
Because we really don't like violence.
No...
NO!
After all, the Shadow Reflector
has been broken into pieces,
Naga and I captured Lagan,
gave him to the Association
and got the two hundred gold coins.
Even though the mirror was broken,
the shadows haven't disappeared.
Nobody knows why they
haven't disappeared.
But what has happened
to the shadows?
You're the girls I met a little
while ago, aren't you?
I underestimated you because
you're girls.
But I won't make that mistake again!
Now, give me twice the amount of
money as last time!
No...
If you see them somewhere,
just forget about it
and say you didn't see
anybody, please.
Please!